{
    "subject": "resource/Zookeeper_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Zookeeper is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by Frank Coraci, starring Kevin James and featuring the voices of Nick Nolte, Sylvester Stallone, Adam Sandler, Judd Apatow, Cher, Jon Favreau, and Faizon Love. The film contains computer animation for the animal characters, it was the first Happy Madison film to be released by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, alongside with Columbia Pictures as usual. The film was released on July 8, 2011.It revolves around an unlucky zookeeper who turns to the animals at his zoo to help him find love. The film received negative reviews from critics and it earned $169.8 million on a $80 million budget.",
    "human_readable": "Zookeeper is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by Frank Coraci, starring Kevin James and featuring the voices of Nick Nolte, Sylvester Stallone, Adam Sandler, Judd Apatow, Cher, Jon Favreau, and Faizon Love.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8390968441963196,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8083918690681458,
            "question": "Name an actor who provides a voice role in Zookeeper."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8065747618675232,
            "question": "Who stars alongside Kevin James in Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7470495104789734,
            "question": "What is the name of the comedy film that features both Nick Nolte and Sylvester Stallone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7264094352722168,
            "question": "What genre is the film Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864902377128601,
            "question": "What year was the film Zookeeper released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6416347622871399,
            "question": "Who plays the lead role in Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5307489633560181,
            "question": "Besides live-action actors, what other type of performers are featured in Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5120517611503601,
            "question": "Can you list three actors who appear in Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47681424021720886,
            "question": "What is the primary plot element of Zookeeper?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zookeeper is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by Frank Coraci, starring Kevin James and featuring the voices of Nick Nolte, Sylvester Stallone, Adam Sandler, Judd Apatow, Cher, Jon Favreau, and Faizon Love.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6016_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you list three actors who appear in Zookeeper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6016_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides live-action actors, what other type of performers are featured in Zookeeper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6016_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who plays the lead role in Zookeeper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6016_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6016_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThis query is a statement about the Zookeeper film, and all the files provided contain information that supports this statement.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents. The description of Zookeeper from multiple files confirms that it is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by Frank Coraci, starring Kevin James and featuring the voices of Nick Nolte, Sylvester Stallone, Adam Sandler, Judd Apatow, Cher, Jon Favreau, and Faizon Love."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}